Natalia Post

55 W 55th st., New York, NY 10019 • 631-561-8295 • nataliapost.nyc@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nataliapost/

SUMMARY

Conscientious, personable, energetic professional with 10+ years of experience in project management, event management, accounting and office management. A born leader, problem solver, and energetic team player. Seeking a challenging role in fast growth organization.

COMPUTER SKILLS

Proficient in Microsoft Office Suite, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, AutoCAD, 20/20, Java, Java Script, HTML, SQL.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Institute for Robotic Process Automation & Artificial Intelligence, New York, $_{\rm NY}$

06/2016 - 11/2019

Executive Coordinator to CEO Frank Casale

- Work directly with IRPA clients and members to arrange meetings, manage communications and take steps to problem solving.
- Accompany and support CEO in business meetings as well as prepare meeting notes and follow ups
- Promoted from assistant to Coordinator after six months of employment.
- Organize conferences, company events, manage projects. Coordinated and organized over a dozen technology focused events ranging from small groups to large forums with over 300 delegates
- Managed membership services and communication for IRPA
- Member of web design team where duties included web page, graphic and content design.
- Attended numerous professional conferences as well as successfully completing a certificate program in Artificial Intelligence (AI).

The Home Depot, Bay Shore, NY

03/2012 - 09/2012

Kitchen and Bath Designer

- Working with clients and providing excellent service in selecting and designing kitchen and bath projects in 20/20.
- Qualify and sell custom cabinet designs and countertops with value added services, such as measuring and installation to retail customers and trade accounts.
- Assist customers looking for fixtures, appliances, countertops, cabinetry, or necessary parts needed for DIY projects and fulfilling special orders through the website or catalogue.
- Initially hired as Associate in Flooring Department, responsible for assisting customers in all flooring projects, window treatments, set up for special order, and quickly promoted to Designer in Kitchen and Bath department.

Bravo Interior, LLC, Moscow,

Russia

08/2010 - 11/2011

Manager/Designer

- Working directly with VIP clients, designers, architects, manufacturers and distributors.
- Responsible for financial services, including Invoice drafting and approval of special terms and conditions.
- Handle accounts payable and accounts receivable.

Mark Wilkinson, LLC, Moscow,

Russia

05/2008 - 08/2010

Designer, Financial Services Manager

- Administrator of financial services, including Invoice drafting and approval of special financial terms and conditions.
- Keep and maintain accounting ledgers via Excel.
- Identifying clients' specific requirements in order to facilitate sales.

MB - Office Equipment, LLC, Moscow,

Russia 03/2006 - 05/2007

Financial Services Assistant

- Clerical duties such as composition of business letters, contracts, invoices, and certificates of completion under direct supervision of company President.
- Accounts receivable and accounts payable.

LEADERSHIP, EXPERIENCE & ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Certificate of Completion The Institute For Robotic Process Automation & Artificial Intelligence - 08/2017 Completed The Next Gen Society: Intro to artificial intelligence.

The National Society of Leadership and Success - Member since 10/2018

Selected by Campus administration to participate among top students in a leadership program including:

- Leadership Training Day: Trained in leadership and success skills via an introspective and interactive training session.
- Speaker events: Participated in seminars led by celebrities and best-selling authors on topics such as leadership, time management, and goal setting.
- Success Networking Teams:
 - o Participated in peer based leadership development teams
 - Experience in setting and achieving goals, receiving coaching, coaching others, and holding others accountable to commitments.

Phi Theta Kappa - member since 10/2018

Selected by Campus administration to participate among top students:

- Participated in team building and leadership enhancing exercises.
- Conducted preliminary research and assisted in brainstorming.
- Organized a personal statement workshop.
- Coordinated events every week.

EDUCATION

Computer Information Systems
Borough of Manhattan Community College, New York, NY 09/16 - 2020

Specialist of Economy (5 year degree) Tolyatti State University of Service, Tolyatti, Russia - 2001-2006